{"data":[{"question":"I am a student of ___.","a":"the Class Second","b":"Class Second","c":"Second Class","d":"Class Two","answer":"4","explain":"\n- You would write \"read the next\/first chapter,\" but \"read Chapter Seventeen,\" etc","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"How many ___ there in the teacher's office?","a":"people are","b":"people is","c":"people has","d":"people have","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Structure: how many\/much + noun+ be there \n- People is plural","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"This big city has had ___ of more than five million.","a":"a large population","b":"the population","c":"Population","d":"populations","answer":"1","explain":"\n+ Large population\/ public...: people in general","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"The mother has bought her daughter a new___.","a":"clothing","b":"clothes","c":"trousers","d":"dress","answer":"4","explain":"- Clothing: clothes to wear (in general)\n\n- Clothes, trousers is plural=> in- Dress: a specific type of clothing","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"Is there ___ in ___ newspaper?","a":"an interesting news, today's","b":"an interesting news, today","c":"interesting news, today","d":"any interesting news, today's","answer":"4","explain":"- News (uncountable): information about something that has happened recently=> cann't not use with \"a\/an\"- We often use \"any\" in interrogative sentence \n\n- Today's newspaper: newspaper of today","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"She had beautiful curly ___ but I could see some gray ___.","a":"hairs, hairs","b":"hair, hair","c":"hairs, hair","d":"hair, hairs","answer":"4","explain":"- Hair (uncountable): implys the whole numbers of hair grow on head (first blank)\n\n- Hair (countable): every\/each hair in grow (second blank)","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"This dictionary is of ___ to students who want to learn English. Well.","a":"much help","b":"many helps","c":"helpful","d":"great helping","answer":"1","explain":"- Help (uncountable)=> cannot use with \"many\"- Helpful (adj)-> cannot use after of\n\n- Helping: the amount of food that someone gives you or that you take","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"The girl broke a ___ while washing up.","a":"wine glass","b":"glass wine","c":"glass for wine","d":"glass of wine","answer":"1","explain":"- Sometimes we use a noun to describe another noun. In that case, the first noun \"acts as\" an adjective:\n\n+The \"noun as adjective\" always comes first and in singular form\n\n+ Structure: two separate words (car door); two hyphenated words (book-case); one word (bathroom)\n\n- This case give more stress on \"glass\", \"wine\" shows the type of glass=> wine glass is more - Glass of wine: give more stress on \"wine\"","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"What you need is more ___ You are always doing your ___ at your desk.","a":"exercises, exercises","b":"exercise, exercise","c":"exercises, exercise","d":"exercise, exercises","answer":"4","explain":"- Exercise: [uncountable] physical activities that you do in order to stay healthy and become stronger\n\n- Exercise: [countable] a movement or set of movements that you do regularly to keep your body healthy","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"Yesterday I called Joe from ___ house.","a":"a friend of my uncle's","b":"one of my friends","c":"Mary's sister's","d":"my aunts'","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Marry's sister's house= House of Marry's sister \n- Aunts= more than one aunt= house shoube be in plural \n- A friend of my uncle's house= unlogical \n- One of my friends: should add possessive \"s\"","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"}]}